<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Liam Hockley]]></title><description><![CDATA[Thoughts and ideas from the mind of a JS and PHP expert]]></description><link>https://liamhockley.me</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 06:48:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[A New Start... Again]]></title><description><![CDATA[What’s Gone? No more Jenkins template-based project. While I do have a reasonable mastery of
Ruby (in particular Rails), I wanted to write…]]></description><link>https://liamhockley.me/a-new-start-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://liamhockley.me/a-new-start-again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 06:15:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;What’s Gone?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No more Jenkins template-based project. While I do have a reasonable mastery of
Ruby (in particular Rails), I wanted to write something based on tools that I
personally prefer (JS, React).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am no longer deep in a job search, so gone is the portfolio and resume links
…for now. I want to focus my efforts on building a single feature first, a Blog,
and committing to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s New?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I rebuilt this website, I wanted to make sure it gave me a platform to truly
put on display my growing mastery of modern JS and related tools and technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to build something statically generated and opted to go with Gatsby for
the task, due to the vibrant plugin market and good support for markdown parsing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had a lot of fun in the process. Much like with my previous Jenkins project,
all my blog posts are simply markdown files. This time I decided I wanted to
write a script to quickly generate a new blog post template.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Next?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next up? Well. This is just, essentially, an “MVP”. I want to add new pages,
features, and continue to polish the layout and styling. I do, however, want the
design to remain minimal. That’s my style, my brand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing I want to do here, is to finally dive into Unit Testing with Jest.
At the moment I have a lot to learn in terms of how to write good unit tests,
in particular how to approach implementation of testing to an existing system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch this space, as there will probably be a blog post (or a few) which talk
about my adventures in Jest.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>